czaqcs.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Bookmark

CzaqcsMark respect and protect the privacy of every individual who uses CzaqcsMark. Individually identifiable information about you is not handed over to third parties without your permission first, as described in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is.

**CzaqcsMark and Cookies**  
In your visit to CzaqcsMark, CzaqcsMark sends a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a collection of data that identifies you as an individual user. CzaqcsMark use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand our user base. CzaqcsMark does this by storing the user’s choice in a cookie and monitor user trends and search patterns. CzaqcsMark will not disclose its cookies to third parties except when it is except if required in legal proceedings such as search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers have settings to accept cookies. You can change your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is sent. Please note, some parts of the Service Locator CzaqcsMark will not work properly if you refuse cookies.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
CzaqcsMark not collect specific information on yourself (such as your name, e-mail address, etc..) Unless you, the knowledge and to your satisfaction, providing such information. CzaqcsMark record and store information such as time, browser type, browser language, and IP address. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

**Identity Data Information Sharing**  
CzaqcsMark may share personal data to other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:

  1. If we have your permission to do that.
  2. The same information is owned by a company or entity believed the purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. This is a subject that requires parties to process information only upon our request appropriate confidentiality. We will not disclose your account information to other people or are not members of the company, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.
  3. If the legislation that we believe is well that such action is necessary to comply with current court, criminal checks, court orders, or legal process served on our Web site.
  4. We may share personal information if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or taking action that sees illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations may require a threat to the physical safety of any person, violations of terms of use, or otherwise required by law legislation.
  5. Third party service providers may require information about the ad serving and email on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and emails received shall be used to improve the service to the user. For this we will also provide information nameless for the sake of improved services.
  6. We may store and process personal information collected on our website or from other agents working on web maintenance services.
  7. We may share general information with partners or other parties without containing the personal data that could be used to contact or identify you personally.

**Rights of Common:**  
We have the right to move any existing data to our designated company and we believe it to store information and assets CzaqcsMark. We reserve the right to change it at all or revise this Privacy Policy at any time.
